You always call it a minority problem, and it's true that black or non-white people are
a minority in any European capital, but we are not a minority in the world.
You are the minority, and that's what you cannot face.
All you really have, after all, are space shuttles, banks, and weapons.
What you don't have anymore is me, and it's only me, me, me, I, the slave, I, the nigger,
I, the black cat, who believed everything you said once.
Nothing you can do will ever persuade me, still less my child, that I am worth less than you.
In the eyes of heaven or in the eyes of earth, it's over.
I have dealt with you a very long time.
Now you've had to deal with me, and I came to stay.
You understand me?
You know?
You wrecked our neighborhoods before we were compelled to come here and wreck your neighborhoods.
You discovered us.
Now you got us.
Do your thing, now, when we have discovered in Amsterdam that we have a minority problem.
You don't.
That we are doing the same thing.
You are doing exactly the same thing, and what you are unable to accept is this.
All right.